Let's go!
Ta-da!
He's so cute.
Wow, here it comes!
It looks so delicious!
I can't stop smiling.
Then I'll make you happy.
Hi, I'm Mizuho Hanyu of Sakurazaka 46.
Today I'm here in Shimokitasawa!
The reason why I came to Shimokitazawa is because it's famous for second-hand clothes and curry.
I often come to Shimokitazawa, but I wanted to go on a date with you all, so I brought you here.
The weather today is so beautiful that it's hard to see the sun.
It's so beautiful today that I'm afraid it's going to be a bit gung-ho without sunshine.
I hope you'll forgive me.
I'm glad I came with you guys.
I like vintage clothing, so I often come to Shimokitazawa.
I often come to Shimokitazawa, so I thought I'd introduce it to you all.
There are a lot of fashionable people in the city, so I like to look at their fashions for inspiration.
I also like to be inspired by their fashions.
Mr. Stylest introduced me to a vintage clothing store that he thought Hanyu would like.
I checked it out, and it's really cute.
I've been paying attention to the store ever since.
So I thought I'd introduce it to you all.
So I thought I'd introduce it to you.
Oh! Here we are!
Ta-da!
Mr. Noil? It's Mr. Noil!
Just go up the stairs and you'll get there!
You're here on a date, right?
Then I'll make you happy!
You can go up first!
Be careful! The stairs are very steep!
Here we go! I counted 100 steps... maybe not 100...
It's only about a hundred steps.
But I'm so excited that I always dance with no problem at all!
Hello!
I'd like to enter the stylish world that awaits us here.
Excuse me. Hello. There are a lot of cool, fashionable waitresses here.Excuse me. Hello. There are a lot of really cool, stylish waitresses here.
Wow, that's great. Then I'd like to take a look.
What's in style right now?
I'm thinking game shirts, game shirts...
It's very fashionable to incorporate sporty elements like this.
I've been paying attention to them, and there are a lot of cute ones.
Isn't this one really cute?
It's so cute!
Half and half.
I think women can wear it without it being too overdone.
So it's pretty stress-free.
You can wear it over a jacket in the fall or winter.
It's cute!
Also, do you know what a rug is these days?
Rugs?
Oh, a carpet.
I've been pulling the carpet down and making pants out of it.
It's so cute!
Like this.
Cute, cute, cute.
So cute!
There's more space between the fabrics than denim or something.
I can wear it lightly in the summer.
It's true, it's true.
It's really nice.
I'd like to show my belly.
It's very summery, isn't it?
It's something that goes with this.
I'll think about it.
A little girly shirt like this. It's so cute.
It's so cute.
I'll show you later how it's set up.
Here I am, all dressed up. So cute!
Oh, my God, I love the layers.
Super cute. Super cute.
This is my first time wearing ragpants.
I usually wear a lot of men's clothes. If I wear too much men's clothes, I'll look like a boy.
No, that's not true. I love it.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is great.
It's perfect. Perfect?
I'm going to check it out. Thank you for having me.
They're so cute. They're so cute.
So many cute things. Oh, my God, these heels.
I'm gonna be about two meters tall by the time I'm done here.
I like hats, too. I always collect hats.
I've always collected a lot of hats. Is this one of Satoru Gojo's?
So let me get this straight.
How's this? I grew my hair back.
T-shirt. I like Tuna Hee.
You can wear it like pants. Wrap it around your waist.
I've been looking for something colored. I have a lot of red and denim, but...
I have a lot of red and denim, but I don't have colored pants. They're cute.
The T-shirts are super cute. I'd love to try them on.
I'd like to try them on one more time.
Let's go!
Ta-da!
Aren't they super cute?
What's wrong with it?
It's so cute!
Ta-da!
How do you like it?
I wrapped the ties around the waist like this...
I tried to make it into pants.
The red color of this Linger Tit
and this pieced together like this...
It's so cute!
I think I like it a lot.
Ta-da!
ta-da!
ta-da!ta-dah!
Ta-da!
ta-da!
Thank you very much.
I will be back.
Great! I bought it.
I love the clothes already and I'm looking forward to wearing them. I'll post it on my Instagram.
I usually buy secondhand clothes when I think they are cute, and I usually agree with the price.
Next, there is a curry shop in Shimokitazawa that I have been wanting to go to.
I got really hungry during the fitting and it was really embarrassing.
This way. I'm looking forward to it.
I like curry very much, and I often make it at home these days.
Do you like curry?
I'm bursting with puns today, too.
Oh! Here we are!
I'm here at Kalpas, a curry and gelato store.
Thank you very much. I was looking forward to meeting you. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to going there.
Looking forward to it.
Hello.
Please.
Wow, great.
You have a meal ticket.
Lots of gelato.
So cute!
Which one shall we have?
Two kinds of curry.
Three kinds.
With gelato?
Curry is good, too.
I'll have the bean curry and the chicken curry.
I think I'll have the chicken.I think I'll have chicken.
I'll have curry, gelato and a drink set.
Thanks for watching.
Have a nice day.
Hello!
Hello. - Hello.
Excuse me.
This looks amazing!
It's like they're famous for their gelato.
Like this.
They have so many kinds of gelato.
Coconut, for example.
There are a lot of gelatos that you don't see very often.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Thank you very much.
Wow!
Looks so delicious!
Look at this!
Oh, my God.
Can I explain?
Dal taluka and bean curry on the left and chicken keemang on the right.
This is the bean curry and the chicken keemang curry.
Oh, my God!
The red one on top of the rice is called chaton stuffed with tomatoes.
The yellow one is pickled lemon with its peel!
If you eat the lemon as it is, it just has a strong sour taste.
If you want to change the taste, mix it with the curry a little bit at a time.
I understand.
Bon appétit!
Wow!
Delicious!
Let's start with the bean curry.
Bon appétit!
Mmmm!
So delicious!
It's insanely delicious!
I don't know...I don't know.
Not too spicy.
Even if you don't like spicy food
I think you can eat it at all.
Delicious!
Then I'll have the chicken one too.
I'll have some chicken too.
Delicious!
It's so deep.
It's like you're going into a cave inside the chicken.
It tastes so good that you want to know the recipe!
It's so delicious!
Shimakutaza is famous for curry.
That's why it looks so good!
I saw it on the Internet and thought it looked really good.
I had already checked out the pictures and everything.
I really wanted to come here.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy to have this opportunity.
It's so delicious!
I often go out to eat alone.
I can go anywhere.
I can travel.
I can go on a trip.
I go to see clothes.
Go to the movies.
I go out to eat.
I do a lot of challenges on my own.
But Otomo went to a family restaurant the other day.
She went to a family restaurant by herself.
I think it's very brave to go to a family restaurant alone.
I think it takes a lot of courage to go alone.
I think there are more people who've never been.
It's a family restaurant.
If you go solo...
I think it's a slow race.
It was delicious!
I finished it.I finished it.
I'm sorry, I'm kind of embarrassed.
I finished it!
It was so delicious!
It was in the top 3 of the curry ranking!
Even if I'm lying, I'm saying it's No. 1.
No. 1, No. 1, yes, No. 1!
I am.
But the chai looks delicious!
Oh! Here it is! Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
It's chai and blue cheese. Please mix the last two together.
Oh, you can mix them?
Yes! Chai and blue cheese!
When you order this, please say "fuzha chai"!
There was a bit of laughter!
Then, let's eat!
Let's start with the chai!
I love chai!
Bon appétit!
Hmm?
Oh!
We're into the story of the chai, aren't we?
What a page in the story!
Wow! It's so delicious!
It's really delicious just the way it is!
I'll have the blue cheese, then!
Bon appétit!
Oh!
Bjorn!
It's so good, it's right under my nose!
It's so good, my nose is runny!
It's so delicious!
I was told to mix this and enjoy the change in taste.
I'd like to try mixing it up a bit.
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!It's so good!
It's so good!
It's like another page has been opened!
It tastes so good that you can be the hero of the story! I'm sure there are some of you who know a lot about curry.
I'm sure some of you know a lot about curry, so I'd love to hear your comments.
Please write a comment! I want to go on a curry tour!
I finished it! Thank you so much for the food!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much for the food. Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
I'm so happy.
It was the best.
We were loaded with what we liked,
A vintage clothing store?
I wore the clothes, I ate curry, and my stomach is happy,
I'm going to have a good dream.
Thank you so much for watching this video.
If you like it, please subscribe to the channel and click the like button.
So, Shimokitazawa, you guys want to go with me?
Please go. Bye bye.